{
    "id": "7e8043d065934eab808299baaba58f6e",
    "title": "Active and Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They ...................... of the function.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have informed",
                "have been informed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "24213fbd519e4fe3a240d423930af9bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher ………………….. the boy for creating trouble in the class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "reprimanded",
                "was reprimanded",
                "has been reprimanded"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "66e3041aaca145cd9da2effe465acb00"
        },
        {
            "question": "Civic authorities ...................... several illegal buildings in the city yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "were demolished",
                "demolished"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d68337af8f494fef8f7991a5d23b2c80"
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………. me of poisoning her dog.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "accused",
                "was accused",
                "was accusing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8b166e11bf064febbfecec051bd076d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The suspect ………………….. to judicial custody.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "remanded",
                "was remanded",
                "has remanded"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4bbf81a3ff0740f89fe3678d826106e5"
        },
        {
            "question": "No one ..................... me a happy birthday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wished",
                "was wished"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9e553d2b553e408eb1480cfa17e21d05"
        },
        {
            "question": "The world ………………… warmer and warmer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is getting",
                "is being gotten"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "32d29ddbd8a447389b161020664408d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "They ..................... to deposit the money.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have told",
                "have been told"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bb9f7e71d20b4ea3b5c37a9d88a54f38"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ..................... to mend my ways.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "told",
                "was told"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "273071c783574aaa9ba5270002accde1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………… anything from them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "haven't heard",
                "haven't been heard"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "289ece7f89f94e88b758d8e7fc4f21c1"
        }
    ]
}